Hello! What's this? A commemorative video?
Oh, this!
I've never had a chance to have so much make-up and costumes prepared for me.
I don't get a chance to have this much make-up and costumes prepared.
I'm going out of town today!
They have such gorgeous lighting and two cameras.
They prepared a sketchbook and other things for us.
It was a very fun shoot!
Thank you so much!
I'm so happy!
Paralila paralila paralila!
I'm fine!
I drove 3 hours from Yamagata today!
I hope it gets shorter soon!
Paralila paralila paralila!
I'm here, I'm here!
My house is in Yamagata
I'm commuting from my parents' house.
I found a lot of frogs and snakes in front of my house.
Then, to my surprise...
They came inside my house!
So I stepped on them.
Yes, on luck!
Using something like an eye-tam as a fashionable
Stylish in a pictorial sense
Stylish, but the content is not.
And the eyebrows are connected.
Your eyebrows are connected.
Eyebrows are connected, too.
So it's not so much about the blur.
It's more about fashion.
Fashion-oriented.
If you don't have enough bokeh...
I'll just use a joke.
But I'm pretty serious about what I'm doing.
I'd like a friend who's pretty introverted.
I like people who stay at home a lot.
I don't follow you if you're quite extroverted.
Point.
Are the eyebrows at your request, Mr. Fujitani?
Yes, I did. He asked me to connect them.
After all, people are connected to each other, aren't they?
That is why I decided on the eyebrows.
I would like to ask Mr. Tachibana if he is mentally OK now.
Ms. Tachibana, you are a little bit troubled.
How is your current mental condition?
I used to be
I used to be a student with a secondary job.
But now I am not.
Gogo.
Yes, I am.
I'm Harima-chan.
Harima-chan.
I've never had a proper conversation with Harima.
I've never had a proper conversation with Harima-chan.
I would like to have a proper conversation with her.
I'd like to have a proper conversation with her.
I don't know.
Yaho Tomato, or
I'd like to have a proper conversation with you.
or "Onsen" (hot springs) in my hometown.
I would like to have a conversation that is not a conversation.
I'd like to have a conversation that isn't a conversation.
Cute.
Really cute.
Pure eyes.
My usual theme for making videos is
Addictiveness
is addictiveness.
Addictive.
Yes, sir.
You said it's close.
It's very close.
Oh!
Security cameras.
Battle.
What? She's been down there the whole time.
That's Mr. Tork.
Always ask for the bright and lucky one.
Q. What is your goal today?
Today is the very day.
Today, I had my outfit prepared, my makeup done, and my hair done.
I also had my hair done in a cute way.
I usually don't have that kind of experience in Sendai Theater.
I don't usually do that at the Sendai Theater, and I don't wear my own makeup, and I don't even wear my own clothes to events.
I joined Starlast to have my hair made pretty, so I am very happy to be able to do this.
I joined Starlast to be made pretty, so I'm very happy to be able to do this.
So you are kind of asking me to do this at the office?
Yes, it was.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, I am.
I'll try harder.
I always thought so.
I think so.
But, you know, we got a lot of customers.
That's about right.
That's right.
Is it changing into something new?
What do you think?
Alternate expectations.Alternate expectations.
Are you feeling pretty good about it?
Yes, I am. I'm really up.
Really?
I am very happy.
Thank you very much.
I'd like you to take some pretty pictures of me afterwards.
That's right. I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I am.
Yuka Nakajima
What is your name, Lucky Fujitani?
It's the name my wife and I used when we were working together.
Oh, so it is your stage name?
Yes, it is.
What is it about your office that confuses you?
I want to be called Lucky. Actually, I want to be called Lucky.
You really want to be called Lucky?
Has that always been the case?
No, for the past two years.
Have you been called Lucky in the past two years?
Yes, I have.
That's good. I'm told that you touch me quite often.
I'll offer you tea.
Is that so?
I'll be the one to bring the tea.
That makes me happy.
Surprisingly, the person who is touching me is hot.
A little hot.
That part is fine.
Is that a no-no?
Will the manager tell me I can't do that?
Are you lucky?
Let's put the last name on it.
I haven't been told anything.
It might become Lucky in the near future.
I actually go by Lucky Fujitani.
I go by Lucky Fujitani.
Lucky Fujitani.
Where did Lucky come from?
Lucky came from the sky.
It came from the sky.
I was inspired by the Paralympics.
I wanted to have fun.
I want to be excited.
It's better to have fun.
Nothing too negative?
I'm actually a negative person.